Guide to the Major Owens collection BCMS.0078
Brooklyn Collection
- Series 8: Photographs and Scrapbooks
  - Photographs (Box 13, Binder 6)
    - TSEP's Nate Williams taping VA award ceremony, July 23, 1978
    - Tenants protesting the moving of NYC housing police out of the developments, August 17, 1978
    - Entrance of 1590 East New York Avenue
    - "Relocate the methodone center" protest
    - Red Cross Brooklyn chapter first aid training
    - Howard Houses Tenant Council meetings
    - MLK, February 1986
      Photographs by Lloyd Terry.
    - Coretta Scott King, 1986
    - Science Fair, Parkside Democratic Club, CORE, Glenwood Houses, May-June 1986
    - Stein Ministries
    - Boys and Girls High School, 1992-1993
  - Photographs (Box 13, Binder 7)
    - Librarians, Stein, Owens, 1985
    - Swearing In, 1985
    - Librarians fundraising, 1984
    - MLK, Prospect Park, Brooklyn Botanic Garden, East Flatbush, 1985
    - Town meeting, May 6, 1986
    - Annette Robins, 1986
    - Department of Labor, June 1986
    - MLK, June 1986
    - Labor, crack rally, Prospect Park MLK, July 2, [1986]
    - Diggers
      Photographs by Lloyd Terry. Features Old Oak angostura bitters.
    - Seniors, August 14, 1986
    - Town meeting, December 9, 1985
    - Boyland
      Includes JHS 263 Black History Month celebration and Jesse Jackson for President campaigning.
    - Book photos
      Includes swearing-in photo and photos with Chuck Schumer and Michael Bloomberg as well as many others.
  - Photographs (Box 13, Binder 8)
    - [Childhood photographs]
    - The Bethune-Dubois Institute
    - Town Meeting, April 21, 1986
      Negatives of photographs by Lloyd Terry.
    - Clara Barton [High School] team
    - Boyland
      Prints, contact sheets and negatives of photographs by Lloyd Terry.
    - Special events and fundraising
      Includes Catherine McAuley HS art winner, Central Brooklyn Martin Luther King Commission, and Jackie Robinson Center for Physical Culture marching steppers.
    - Community Church
    - Haitian Action Lobby, February 14, 1986
    - Open House for Andrew Stein, August 3, 1985
      By Leslie Fratkin.
    - Rev. Elijal Pope
  - Photographs, Duplicates (Box 14, Binder 9)
  - Photographs, Duplicates (Box 14, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, Community Development Agency, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Community Development Agency, 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, Community Development Agency, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Major Owens and S. Wendell Claude, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mounted Photographs, c1975 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - Mounted Photograph (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Oversize Photographs (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Series 9: Audiovisual
  - Cassettes, 1983-1999 (Box 16, Cassette 1-9)
  - Compact Discs (Box 16, Disk 1-3)
  - VHS Tapes, 1986-2005 (Box 17, Item 1-15)
  - VHS Tapes, 1987-2004 (Box 18, Item 1-15)
  - Floppy Disks, 1980-2007 (Box 19, Disk 1-65)
- Series 10: Awards
  - ACGIH Award, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Awards, Various, 1999-2004 (Box 20, Item 1-7)
  - Awards, Various, 1980-2006 (Box 21, Item 1-13)
  - Awards, Various, 1983-1995 (Box 22, Item 1-4)
  - Awards, Various, 2001-2004 (Box 23, Item 1-5)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Barber-Scotia College Prayer Brunch, 2007 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - The Bethune-DeBois Institute, 2000 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - Black/Jewish Congressional Reception, 2002 (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Board of Count Commissions, Miami (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Division of Child Protection (Box 29, Item 1)
  - Morehouse College (Box 30, Item 1)
  - National Association of Community Health Centers (Box 31, Item 1)
  - Martin Luther King Government Responsibility Award (Box 32, Item 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 33, Item 1)